Jacob Hukari

Denver, Colorado (720) 579-7380 hukarijake@gmail.com

I have had a great interest in hacking/coding since I was a very young child, I decided to teach myself HTML, CSS, javascript, PHP, and MySQL when I was 10 years old and have since greatly improved my skills, I never wanted to go to college because I felt like it wouldn t be necessary, I instead chose to work as hard as I could to improve my skills and myself as a person, I've always enjoyed working for small companies however my dream is to someday own my own company.

Work Experience

Web Developer

02/2019 to 08/2019

Maltronics

Remote

I worked as a full-stack web developer for a cybersecurity product company called "Maltronics" I really enjoyed my time there, however; I decided to leave and pursue something I enjoyed more.

Web Security Consultant

09/2020 to 01/2021

EDEC

Remote

I did security for a company called EDEC which sells security products for a few months, the job was great however I decided to leave and spend time working on personal projects.

Security Vulnerability Expert

10/2020 to 10/2020

Buffalo Trace Labs

Remote

I found a security vulnerability on the Buffalo Trace Distillery which allowed me to access all of the companies data and security cameras, I reported this vulnerability and was hired to fix it.

Web Developer

12/2020 to 01/2021

GameBarrier

Remote

I did full-stack Web Development for a gaming startup called "GameBarrier" I only worked for them for a few months because the company was very unprofessional, my experience there was not great but they said that they really liked my web dev ability.

Freelance Full-Stack Web Development and Website Security

01/2018 to Present

Self-Employed

Remote

I work from home doing full-stack website building and website security, I can drop this at any time in place of a full-time job so it will not get in the way.

Skills

Full-Stack Backend Website Development - 4 years

Full-stack Frontend Website Development - 4 years

Python - 3 years

Django - 2 years

Security Consulting - 2 years

Full-stack Database Administration - 3 years

Software Engineering - 3 years

Vulnerability Analysis - 3 years

Education

George Washington High School

High school or equivalent Computer Science Denver, Colorado